It appeared as if humanity will soon
be destroyed by the demons.
But there was a mage who fought alone
and saved everyone.
He was called the Magic Emperor
and became a legend.
You see...
even a commoner can win too.
Can you see how powerful we can be?
Asta!
What a ridiculous guy.
So you are finally awake. you jerk?
Has my magic been sealed off?
When we get back to Magic Knights.
I want you to spill it all out.
Who are you and what's your motive?
I refuse.
It looks like the end is here.
Ice Magic. Ice Funeral.
Where does his determination come from?
What an asshole!
Life...
What does he take life for?
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
You guys are so screwed.
Why does he seem so happy?
Someone just died.
Captain. this isn't the time to laugh.
Even if we're upset.
Mr. Seihi wouldn't come back alive.
Right?
Yes. Yami is right!
Mr. Seihi has always loved
a lively environment.
Come on! Laugh!
Laugh!
Louder!
You too. Noelle!
This is great.
What happened to Mr. Seihi
was a real shame.
but all of you managed
to protect the villagers.
Be proud of yourselves.
All of you did well.
and I thank you for that. you fools.
-Yes!
Thank you.
What's with that hand gesture?
You fool!
Don't you even know
the salute of the Magic Knights?
Take a good look!
These fingers represent the clover.
Come on! Try it!
Yes!
You sure are a quick learner!
I'm back!
Thank you for your hard work.
Vanessa! Finral!
Yami. we've been
to the Magic Investigation Department.
I see. Did you find out anything?
Where did those people come from?
We must find their base
and teach them a good lesson!
We need to take care
of that jerk who got away too.
About that...
The Investigation Department identified
the item left behind by the perpetrator.
But there's still no clue yet.
The Investigation Department
is so useless.
Hey. you!
Don't break anything!
So sorry.
But that pocket watch
looks quite precious. right?
Yes. and judging from your statement
about their words and deeds.
they seem to be of high status.
So. they are either royals or nobles?
My goodness.
Where did he come from? He's so cute!
How is it cute?
It's really cute!
It hurts!
Damn it!
Here. Come here.
You ugly birdie!
I'm going to fry you!
I won't let you do that!
Come to your senses!
Didn't I tell you not to do that?
Are you trying to tear down this building?
-Sorry!
You're clearly the one
who did the most damage!
All right. May I have your attention?
It doesn't matter if the perpetrators
are royals or nobles.
It's the same.
We'll just leave it
to the Investigation Department.
We'll just wait for the report.
Enough said about that.
I have some good news.
-Good news?
Would you like to know?
Sure!
Your performance has gained recognition
from the Magic Emperor.
The Magic Emperor?
So. you've been given a star.
For real?
Awesome!
It's great!
Not bad.
Congratulations.
Well. what do we do with the stars?
Don't get all excited
if you don't know what it is.
Stars are awarded by the Magic Emperor
based on performance.
What are they for?
This is like an honor.
An honor?
That's right. Asta.
It's an honor.
It's an honor for the men.
There are girls here too.
It's an honor for both men and women!
I don't follow.
The Magic Knights will compete
in terms of the number of stars earned.
Because that shows
how much work a squad has done.
I see!
Besides. Golden Dawn is currently
at the top with 70 stars.
Seventy stars?
What about us?
How many does the Black Bull have?
We can't lose to the Golden Dawn!
As for us...
We'll have a negative 30 stars
with this added to the collection.
Negative?
What?
We're 100 stars away from the Golden Dawn.
One hundred?
It's a long way to go
to catch up to them. Yuno.
It's impossible.
Is it really a good idea for me
to continue staying in this squad?
Also. there's one more thing.
It's the pay for this month.
It's money!
There are 200.000 yuls!
Thank you!
Thank you. Captain!
That way.
I can eat a lot of delicious food!
Sure. eat all you want.
Hey. Captain!
How much do I have to pay you
to get you to fight me?
Name your price.
No. thanks.
Come on.
I want to buy a new outfit for my goddess.
which is my sister. Marie.
Which do you think suits her better?
Don't ask me.
I don't know.
You get a day off tomorrow.
Don't squander away all your money.
I'm going on dates with the girls.
As you wish.
Thank you. Captain!
Captain. thank you for looking out for us!
I would like to hang out with you guys.
What do you think?
He's only giving us this much money.
What nonsense is that?
With this much money.
I can be ten years' worth of nomotatoes!
Nomotatoes?
What are those?
It is a kind of sweet potato
that is native to Hage Village
which has an indescribable taste.
It sounds so gross.
Not at all!
Sister Lily can make anything taste good!
Who's that?
She's the one
I'm going to marry in the future!
What?
But aren't sisters part of the clergy?
I don't think they can get married.
There's always a way to go about it.
I want to go beyond the limits!
You're a fool!
Congrats on getting your first pay!
How are you going to spend it?
I haven't thought about it.
What about you. Little Boy?
I want to send it back
to the church at Hage Village.
I see. That's really good. Asta.
That's what a real man is.
You think so too?
Magna. are you sending it back too?
Of course.
But...
But?
That will have to wait
until I've increased it a hundredfold.
This guy never learns.
If you are a real man. you have to gamble!
Instead of a real man.
you should just call yourself a fool.
It's good that you send it back.
but hopefully not all of it.
Keep some for yourself.
Really?
But what should I spend it on?
Let's go shopping
in the castle town tomorrow.
You too.
I'll take you there.
-All right.
Sister Lily. how are you?
I'm doing great here.
My seniors are taking great care of me.
Asta. stand right here.
What for?
Don't move around.
Fire Magic!
Exploding...
Fireball!
It's so hot!
Didn't I tell you not to move around?
I didn't move!
Also. I performed well
for my first mission...
and gained a star from the Magic Emperor
for my performance.
If this goes on. I might become
the Magic Emperor next month.
I want to be the Magic Emperor
and make this world
a happy place for everyone.
Then. I'll come back for you.
Please marry me!
Right. I'm sending back my first paycheck.
Done!
It's all done!
I'm really good at writing letters!
Sister Lily will surely be so touched
that she shed tears.
The Magic Emperor.
The Magic Emperor?
I wonder what kind of person he is.
Have you been to the castle town?
-No.
-It makes sense.
The royals or nobles rarely go
to places where commoners live.
What about you. Little Boy?
I merely passed by that place
to take the Magic Knights Entrance Exam.
Well. enjoy yourself today.
Come on! Don't simply touch around!
What can I do?
If I don't hold on tight.
I'm going to fall!
I just seem to care a lot. Damn it.
Oh no.
Not again?
The Clover Kingdom
is split between the Noble Realm.
where the royals and nobles live.
Then. there's the Common Realm
where the commoners live.
and the Forsaken Realm
where the lowly live.
Kikka. the castle town
where Asta and Yuno participated...
in the Magic Knights Entrance Exam
is in the Common Realm.
It's indeed very lively.
It's so crowded.
I wish I could bring Sister Lily
and the kids in the church here someday.
What about me?
Marie. my goddess.
I'm coming over now.
I can't hold back anymore.
I wish to see the smile on your face soon.
Father!
This voice...
You're back again this month.
Here I am again.
I won't lose this time.
So am I!
Here's the super large serving
with everything on it!
Let's see if you finish them all!
I'm digging in!
Just the sight of it
makes me want to throw up.
Miss. are you free?
Would you like to have a drink with me?
Do I look like I'm free?
You can bring your kids along.
I know a great place--
These aren't my kids!
They are my siblings!
We're rushing back to open the store.
We don't have time for this!
Tough women aren't that bad either.
Miss. would you like to join me?
Little boy. don't walk too fast
on your own!
It makes me feel so excited!
Are you really not going to buy anything?
No. there are too many things!
I don't know what to buy!
Not for me.
Hey. look at the robes.
Aren't they the Magic Knights?
That symbol...
Seriously? The Black Bull?
That's Vanessa. the Drunken Frenzy Witch.
Are that cute girl and that little brat
the members of the Black Bull too?
It's better for us to stay away from them.
What's with the noises all of a sudden?
Ignore them.
As long as there are Magic Knights.
it helps to curb crime.
Besides. some nice guys
might come approaching us.
We've bought the healing herbs
and the shique ointment for disinfection.
That's all for now.
We've got what we needed.
Let's go somewhere quiet.
Somewhere quiet?
It's my personal collection.
This is it!
Here?
But it's just a small alley.
It's a dead end.
What?
All right! Quickly come over!
That was close.
BLACK MARKET
This is the Black Market.
The Black Market?
This place is a little dangerous.
but it has great magic tools
that are super effective.
Hey. Vanessa.
I've brought in some good stuff.
Awesome. Show me later.
This is so awesome!
What's wrong?
You don't seem to be interested.
No.
But it's no surprise.
because the royals and nobles
wouldn't come to places like this.
But you still can't control
your magic. right?
That's right. But how are these related?
There might be a magic tool in the market
that will help you control your magic.
As long as you can find
the magic tool that suits you.
you might be able to control it.
Control my magic power?
Let's try to find it. All right?
Sure!
Why is it so lively over there?
It's still too soon for you to go there.
If amateurs aren't careful in there.
they might get screwed over.
All right!
Here I come!
I'll use my paycheck
and increase it a hundredfold!
I met someone I know!
Damn it! I lose again!
That's because I can see the future.
That old lady is really good.
Anyway. it's not the time for this now.
I should get back to work.
They called it a job.
but it's actually
to catch the pickpockets.
Is this something
that the Magic Knights should do?
But the captain is so scary.
I dare not disobey him.
Kiddo. do you have any objections?
Beware. I'll cut you into two!
I finally made it into the Magic Knights.
but it feels so miserable.
It's the Green Mantis.
It's a mantis.
A bug.
I have to work my ass off
every single day.
Even if I go on a mission.
I've to risk my life to be a bait.
I get constipation
and going bald because of that.
Damn it.
She's so cute!
How about this?
It looks like it can be used
to stabilize your magic power.
It looks awful.
Don't say that. Try it on first.
It's your fault for standing there!
I didn't expect to see you here!
What's the matter?
The Black Market doesn't seem
like a place for pretty girls like you.
Are you lost?
Allow me. the elite members
of the Magic Knights. to lead you outside.
Get lost. you flying insect.
Hey! I found an interesting item!
Don't tell me you're buying that!
It can talk!
He bought it.
Look!
We are humans!
Right?
So what?
This little brat...
Wait. Aren't you Haha?
I'm Sekke! Not Haha!
Haha. how have you been?
I told you! I'm Haha...
No. I mean. Sekke!
Who is he?
Someone I met at the entrance exam.
I see. He's a member of the Green Mantis.
Are these two pretty ladies with him?
If so.
these two must be members
of the Black Bull.
Asta. you bastard.
Despite being in the Black Bull.
you're making me jealous.
Come to think of it.
it's all your fault that I ended up
in the Green Mantis.
How infuriating.
Thief!
My winning prize!
Stop right there!
-Petite Clover!
Sekke's Haha Lecture!
"Haha!"
-"Haha!"
-No. that's not right.
"Haha!"
You're still far
from that level of "Haha".
"Haha!"
What's "Haha"?
Here comes the chance
to do a deed of merit!
I want to catch the pickpocket
and gain stars from the Magic Emperor.
Black Clover. Page 12.
"The Magic Emperor Saw."
My "Haha" is in never giving up!
Subtitle translation by Angel Choo
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm